the five easiest last minute Halloween
costumes that take less than 5 minutes
to make the cial killer take a Serial
box and a harmless plastic knife or
sword and step it into the cereal box
then attach everything to a t-shirt or
hoodie the fourth easiest hin costume
the Identity Thief wear a regular outfit
write name tags with different names and
stick them all over the outfit number
three the pumpkin pie take an orange
t-shirt print out the number pie this
way you can pull out the first 500
digits of pie number two the quarterback
take a T-shirt and a quarter dollar and
tape it to the back but the easiest hin
outfit is still the nerd it requires
only a single sheet of paper write four
or four costume not found on it and
attach it to a hoodie perfect for all
the tech NS who forgot to call their
outfit on time